So, I'm going to say something and say
some words of courage, but all I have to
say is
set it and forget it. That's all I got
to say. It's week five of me trying to
turn $100 into a million day trading.
Last week, we ended up taking two
unnecessary losses because I broke my
trading plan. You good?
Oh, that that doesn't seem very good.
[sighs]
That's why we have the Punisher. Every
single time that I break my trading
plan, I have to drive this car for 24
hours. Last week, the account was at
$15,000 and we were trying to take it to
$30,000.
But now, we are left off with $9,000
because we lost $6,000 last week on two
crazy trades that we broke our trading
plan on. So annoying. Market update.
Currently right now, 9:26
in the morning. Not good. Currently, we
are down. Let it load. Let it load.
$3,000. So,
[__]
And last week, we learned a lot from
those two losses. Those losses were
lessons learned for now this week to
take these $9,000 that we have in the
account up to $18,000.
Let me tell you, I see some great market
op-
Oof. I smell like ass. Let's go to the
markets and go see these good
opportunities. Let's go.
Good morning, ladies and gentlemen. It
is officially week number five turning
$100 into a million. Ah, [__] You going
to have to Oh, you heard it? You going
to have to add some more major cracking
noise.
Yeah. This week, we got to make up for
last week's [__]
[__] slack. Oh, that's the couch
chair. You got to blame yourself. You
got to hit your chair.
We actually got a new chair, by the way.
So, this time we're going to auction it
off for $5 million cuz I've made over $5
million trading in this chair. So,
whoever buys it can also make $5 million
in this chair. We're going to build that
chair probably today or tomorrow.
Week number five. We're back at it. All
right, guys. So, this is week number
five.
Starting balance right now of the
challenge Oh, by the way, if you guys
look see think that I'm red, it's
because I went to Bimini on a boat.
2 hours to cross the Atlantic Ocean from
the United States to the Bahamas. We
crossed this right here and this is the
from Miami
to Bahamas. That is the
ocean with no name.
Wait, or maybe it has a name. I don't
know. But the point is that we crossed
it. We got sunburned. But now, we're
back this week. Starting balance for the
week is going to be Drumroll, please.
$8,949.
So, last week we took two losses on the
challenge, which absolutely suck. They
were unnecessary losses and we paid the
price for those losses, which is our new
vehicle that we have gotten, which is a
Volkswagen and the name is this right
here. I don't know the name yet. We're
going to be deciding by today or
tomorrow. So, editors are going to edit
it in. And every single time I break my
trading plan, I have to drive that
Beetle for 24 hours. And whether I win
or lose, if I take a trade against my
trading plan and I win, I still have to
do it because I broke my trading plan.
And if I take a trade and I lose, I
still have to do it because I broke my
trading plan. Holding myself
accountable. Taking myself back to the
roots. So, this week we actually have
some interesting markets, some
repetitive ones from the last weeks. And
then we've actually added some cryptos
into the chart because I'm actively
looking to invest into some type of
crypto, but we'll probably drop that
later throughout the day. So, let's
start off with pairing number one is
going to be GBPUSD.
So, GBPUSD
as of right now on the weekly time
frame, we are currently having a
beautiful retest of this previous
structure level right here. Very strong
double weekly doji and it clearly this
move right here is bullish on the weekly
time frame. And we can anticipate a push
for the upside. If I simply get this
line chart right here and I take it to
the structure point, which are the
bodies of these candlesticks, you can
very clearly see how well structured
this looks. Any textbook trade will tell
you that that right there is setting up
for a buy. It simply makes more sense
for this trade from this point right
here to head to the upside versus to the
downside. Cuz that's all we're trying to
do at the end of the day with this
challenge. Especially after two weekly
dojis.
But, you then go down to the daily time
frame
and we can clearly see that we are under
this very strong level of support and
resistance and also this EMA, which can
indicate to us that the daily time frame
can potentially have a rejection to this
point right here. And then when you go
down to the 4-hour time frame, the
4-hour time frame is kind of in the
middle. It's kind of rejecting, but now
it's breaking above. I personally want
to take this trade as a buy with the
higher time frame of the weekly. So, in
order for me to do that, I would have to
wait for this time frame to body close
above, retest, and then head to the
upside.
Cuz that is literally exactly what it
did right here. We broke up, retested,
and headed to the upside. Whenever we
are under, we head to the downside.
Whenever we are on the upside, we head
to the upside. Whenever we're above, we
head to the upside. So, in this case, I
got to wait for it to get to the upside.
If not, I'm going to be looking for some
potential sells once we kind of break
out of this little inwards triangle. So,
I mentioned in the last uh 100 to the
million challenge that I hate trend
lines, that trend lines are subjective.
Trend lines, you can literally put them
from wick to body,
body to wick, wick to wick, body body,
and it's just extremely subjective and
it there's no real strategy behind trend
lines. It kind of just gives you an idea
of what the market is moving like. Is it
moving in a upwards channel, in a
downwards channel? Is it moving in a
triangle like is it consolidating into
one spot where it's going to potentially
break out? But I would not ever use a
strategy based off of trend lines. So,
for all all of the you guys that asked
on why I don't use trend lines, it's
because it's so subjective. For example,
I can literally use the trend line from
wick, right? Let's say we start off from
this wick. So then, let's say we're
going to use this wick as a
continuation. Or if you do it like that,
this looks completely different. Or if
you put it to the highest wick, then it
looks like this. Or you do it to it to
that wick, it just looks completely
different. But then let's say we do it
to the bodies and we do it to this body
right here. Oh, yeah, it broke and
retested out. Or if you do it to then
this next body, it's like, "Oh, it's
breaking out to the upside." It's just
too subjective, right? So, I don't
really like using it as a confluence. I
just kind of use it to get a visual
visualize understanding of where the
market is actually squeezing into. So,
basically, I use this trend line to
identify this market right here that the
only way I would be interested in
selling is if you have some type of
breakout like this, which realistically,
all that matters it's going to be a
break and retest of this structure point
right around here. So, looking for the
temporary sells, they can be short-term
sells from this point to then this point
right around here. And then down here,
we can potentially be interested in buys
to execute over the long run.
Or we can just wait for the break and
retest above to then take this trade to
the upside. That's GBPUSD. Next is going
to be NZDUSD.
So, I [__] hate
this [__] because I always analyze the
markets on Sunday with the students.
Yeah, I get on a call on every single
Sunday with my students for like 2 hours
where I literally break down every
single one of these markets. So, look.
You guys can have an idea.
I don't only trade just these markets
right here. I analyze all of these
markets right here. And out of all these
markets, I find the best trading
opportunities in them and which one have
the highest probability in going in one
direction versus the other using my
strategy.
And by the time that I'm done with that
call, it's 2 hours, I'm [__] drained
because there's thousands of students
that join. They ask a bunch of
questions. And I'm always like, "We'll
start the series on Monday, right? We'll
start it tomorrow." Don't want to start
it Sunday night cuz I'm just tired. The
energy's not there.
And this [__] happens where the trades
play out right before I can even begin
on Monday. So, this one yesterday, we've
identified NZDUSD
that it was retesting this beautiful
level of support and resistance. So,
clearly whenever above, we're going up.
Whenever we're under, we're going down.
Whenever we're above, we're going up.
Clearly, we're above and all we were
waiting for is for price to body close
above this structure point right here.
So, a body close structure point right
around here,
then we would be interested in a buy.
So, we would have entered this trade
right around here. But obviously, it
played out extremely fast, which kind of
sucks because, you know, you guys can't
see it. I personally didn't catch it cuz
it was very late. I already know
students in the Discord caught it
because they have different time zones
all around the world. And you know, but
when I'm sleeping, they're awake. So,
currently right now, what I'm waiting on
NZDUSD
in order for me to enter this trade
safely is going to wait for a retest of
this structure level. So, the ideal
entry would have been here. But now, the
only way I could enter is if we have
this retest to then head to the upside.
So, I can be very patient on this trade.
Next is going to be NZDUSD.
So, this is going to be a absolutely
beautiful trade. So, you guys can tell
here on NZDUSD, we are bearish on this
daily time frame cuz we body closed
under that structure point and then the
weekly time frame is bullish. You can
clearly see that the weekly time frame
had a high, a pullback, and then here it
can have uh potentially have a push to
the upside. Daily timeframe, we are
clearly rejecting this level of
resistance. Resistance can now
potentially be used as support. And what
a coincidence, we also have that daily
EMA. So, we've had a very strong push,
and the pullback has started to slow
down right around this area. Now, this
is setting up a absolutely beautiful
trade that is going to be one sweet body
close above this zone. Then, once we
have the retest, we can enter this
trade. Now, what's that going to look
like? That's going to look like a very
nice juicy daily bullish engulfing
candlestick. Then, after that bullish
engulfing candlestick, all we have to do
is wait for a little quick retest to
then take this trade to the upside. This
is by far going to be a very, very clean
and solid trade as of right now from
what I can tell. It's already having a
reaction. But, we cannot buy right into
resistance. This is clearly a level of
resistance. It's pushed prices to the
downside, so we can't just buy right
into that. We have to confirm that once
price has broken above that, we retest
it and continue heading to the upside.
Next is going to be GBP/CAD.
We analyzed this last week for sales,
and we missed it. But, this week we are
interested in now buys because that was
the countertrend trade pullback. Now, we
can be interested in taking the trade
[music] to the upside. You got to be
realistic and ask yourself, after such a
strong weekly bearish candlestick like
this, do you think the next week is just
going to completely engulf that?
Probably not. It's just not ideal. It's
probably going to need one weekly doji
candlestick of just slow move here, and
then the next week we can potentially
have the push. Exactly how we did right
here. It's pulled back two candlesticks,
one week it chilled, then the next week
it then had the push. The exact same
thing, but now here we just have to be
extra patient. So, for that I'm going to
be waiting for price to have a very
clean break and retest to head to the
upside on this market right here.
Next is going to be EUR/USD, which we
analyzed since that last week as well.
To keep it very simple, we took the
degenerate sales on this market right
around here, and we got stopped out.
But, now we're going to continue to wait
for the pullback here. We're not going
to
[music]
force this trade. And once we get here,
then we'll be interested in the buys.
So, at this point we'll be looking to
then buy this market. And then the next
market are uh EUR/AUD and EUR/GBP, but
they're like so far out from being
tradeable that there's no point in
wasting time actually breaking them
down.
So, that's exactly what it's going to
look like. Let me show you guys the My
FxBook to start off the week. So, as you
guys can see, this is a real account.
You can tell by the starting balance
that we are $8,449.
And you guys can tell down here that
currently we have a profitability of a
71%,
meaning that 70% of the trades we win,
30% of the trades we lose, and 100% of
the trades that we have taken have been
a short. So, we have not taken any long
positions so far in the challenge. And
our average duration on a trade is 20
hours and 48 minutes. This is just This
is actually longer before, but simply
because the losses that we took were
obviously fast. You know, we pretty much
entered a trade within the day we got
stopped out. That's why that time
actually went down a bit because, you
know, it was a bit higher. It's almost
like 2 days.
But, I guess because of the losses it
averaged it out a little bit
differently. But, yeah, this is day one
of the [__] week five. The goal is to
take these $9,000 pretty much up into
$18,000,
which sucks because that literally just
puts us about $3,000 above last week's
starting balance. So, this week what
we're basically doing it for our honest
to God for this week is to recuperate
what we lost all of last week and just
put us a tiny bit above. So, currently
right now it is 8:51 in the morning.
And
let's see where today takes us. All
right, so we just ordered a new chair.
So, I've had the same chair for about, I
don't know, like a year. The last chair
that I had, I made over a million
dollars, then I got rid of it. So, now
you have it. And now this next chair,
I've already made over 10 million
dollars. So, now I'm going to get rid of
it. Now, this is a new chair where my
goal is to make 25 million dollars. So,
the previous chair was uh like a It was
Shaquille O'Neal's chair. It's a really
big, comfy office chair. Really bad for
my lower back, so hopefully this is more
comfortable. This is not an ad. Like,
I'm not even going to promote them. I
just want to see if it's actually If
it's actually comfortable, I'm going to
obviously shout them out and [__] But,
I have had, I think, 15 different office
chairs, and none of them last more than
a week just because they suck. The last
Obviously, the two that I just mentioned
were the best ones that I stuck with the
longest. But, if I use it for 2 3 days
and I don't like it, I literally just
throw it away. So, we're going to build
this [__] real quick.
It's black. I thought I ordered it
white.
[music]
Passes the vibe check.
I don't know. How does it look?
It looks like a regular chair. Does it
Does it really?
Yeah, I mean, it looks like a regular
office chair.
Um
It looks like a Costco chair. That's
what it looks like. Yeah, I feel like a
[__]
I feel like a 9-to-5er in this [__] I
definitely feel like my posture is
better, though.
So, at least like
this does hug the [__] out of me.
But, then it doesn't stay stuck.
What do you think?
Hey.
You have like a collection of chairs
going on in here. Yeah, so this is uh
your guru's chair.
This is your mentor's chair right here.
This is what they They're small and
soft.
Cuz they're small and soft.
See the connection there? So, this is
the old one, right?
Made 10 million dollars in this chair.
Now, is this going to be the chair where
we make 25 million dollars?
Honestly, I don't know. Yo, but now that
I'm sitting here in it, it's It's
actually feeling very, very comfortable.
Like
I feel like I can actually [__]
pull up here.
I don't know.
Like, my arms aren't super down.
All right, let's see how it feels. Do a
quick trade update.
So, right now currently it is Choose
this phone. It is currently
8:57. Whoa, can't show you guys a new
car.
Whoa, Alex got a new car.
Interesting.
Well, let me tell you this right now.
I got more than a new [__] car. I
can't say.
I can't say.
All right, let's just say I'm going to
crack the [__] internet. You know
what? This is a hint right here. This is
a hint right here. If you know,
you [__] know. Another Tesla? I I I
don't know.
I don't know. Trade update. So, it's
currently 8:57 in the evening
or in the in the night. Oh, this is
already Oh, this is already a problem.
All right, we're going to put it lower.
We're in here. All right, perfect. All
right, so trade update. We have GBP/USD
as the number one pair. So, obviously
earlier we were looking at these
countertrend trades, and we did not take
them simply because it did not have the
break and retest under the structure
level like I mentioned. So, we're simply
going to continue to wait for that in
order to take this countertrend trade if
we decide to. If not, we're going to
wait for the break and retest above to
head to the upside. Next is going to be
NZD/USD,
where
where we've had the push, very strong
daily bullish engulfing candlestick.
Now, in order for me to enter this
trade, I simply need to wait for this
next daily candlestick to have
a pull back to this area so I can
actually find an entry. So, it'll look
like that on the daily, a daily wick.
Then, on the 4-hour, it'll look just
like a little more of a 4-hour pullback
retracement into here to head to the
upside. So, actively waiting on that.
USD/CAD, we've had a very nice daily
bullish engulfing candlestick rejection
of the EMA.
Not as strong as I'd want it to close. I
would want it to close stronger, but we
got to do what we got to do.
And then, we have a somewhat of a
[__] the structure, but I want it to
break above this and then have the
retest. Just need more confirmations.
And then lastly, GBP/CAD, we're going to
be waiting for a better break and retest
above. So, technically right now, the
only one that is actively looking close
to being ready is USD/CAD
and
GBP/USD.
So,
just to show you guys, actively right
now, we have no trades on the account,
and it is 9:00 p.m. EST. I don't believe
any trades are going to be ready tonight
in London session. It's still very
early. So, we'll probably have to check
back in in the morning tomorrow, and
let's see what happens then. So, I'm
going to test out the chair throughout
the whole night. [laughter]
And then
I thought the same thing
earlier. So, we're going to test it out,
and then we'll let you guys know how it
is tomorrow. Check in in the morning.
All right, guys, trade update. So, day
one with the new chair. I don't know. I
don't know if you guys
understand, but there's a really big
importance of the office chair. It's
like
I spend more time on this chair than in
my bed. So, it's a very big deal that
you have the right and ideal chair
because this is what's going to make you
feel comfortable so you make the [__]
[__] money, you know what I'm saying?
Currently right now, trade update, it is
currently 10:19 in the morning. So, last
night, kind of like I mentioned, we
weren't going to be interested in taking
any trades. The account is currently
still sitting at
the same balance. We haven't taken
absolutely no trades, but we might take
a trade in the next 40 minutes. So, pay
attention. First trade is going to be
USD/CAD,
where currently we are having the little
pullback that I mentioned. Very nice
daily bullish engulfing rejection
candlestick. The 4-hour is pulling back
exactly how I would love for it to pull
back. And it looks like we're closing
with a 4-hour bullish engulfing
candlestick. Obviously, we still have 2
hours and 39 minutes until that
candlestick closes. For me to enter this
trade right now, I literally just need
this candlestick to body close above
that neckline right there, cuz it
created pretty much a double bottom. And
then it would be the breakout of that
double bottom and pretty much confirm
that this might be the area where it
could push through this zone right here.
Now, it is a higher risk trade because
I'm technically buying right into this
level of resistance. Clearly, it is used
as a level of resistance and it is
respected all throughout here. So, the
ideal trade is actually once it breaks
above it, then it retests it, then this
is where we should be entering when we
use this as a support. So, it is a bit
of a higher risk trade,
but [__] it. Now, it's not a trade that
I'm breaking my rules. Keep in mind, I
am following my rules. I'm not taking a
countertrend trade. I'm buying at an
area of interest, I have my entry
signal, everything that I look for in a
trade, trend, everything.
Now, it's just a higher You guys got to
understand the meaning of that. There's
a big difference in between a high-risk
trade and a trade that does not follow
your trading plan. Taking a high-risk
trade doesn't mean that you're breaking
your trading plan. The way I grade my
trades in my trading plan, I can give it
a So, I every single trade is graded,
right? It's either graded 100%, 90%,
80%, 70% based off of how many
confluences we can add into this market
to make it make more sense that it's
going to go in one direction versus the
other. Now, if it's a very low-graded
trade, that means that it's a higher
risk trade. So, let's say, for example,
this trade has a total of five
confluences, right? That would be a 50%
grade, which in the US, that's a D. Pop
up here the grading system in the United
States of America. This is what I barely
graduated high school with. So, 50% is a
bad grade, which means that it's a
higher risk trade. Now, let's say we
were to get 80% on this trade in terms
of points and, you know, things that we
were to add to confluences, now this has
a Now, it's Now, it's not as high of a
risk trade because you have more
confluences for it to go in one
direction versus the other. So, this is
a higher risk trade because it doesn't
have that many points. Does that [__]
make sense? Makes sense. All right, if
you understood, let me know in the
comments below. But the point is that
we're looking to enter this trade very
soon. Next is EUR/AUD. So, I know this
wasn't on the watchlist earlier this
week, but we just added it right now.
Well, it was at the bottom of our
watchlist, but we just didn't prioritize
it cuz it didn't look that clean. Now,
we're actually going to implement it. I
don't love the daily timeframe simply
cuz we're bullish, but we are under this
very strong level of resistance,
resistance, resistance, support,
resistance. Clearly, whenever we're
under, we're rejecting. Whenever we're
above, we're rejecting to the upside.
And right now, we're clearly under. I
love how the 4-hour is bearish and it's
creating these very clean lower, lower,
lower high legs. Now, we have a pullback
right into this level of resistance, how
we did here, break, retest, and we can
expect that sell. Break, retest, and we
literally expect that same [__]
sell. Did you see here? Two little
candlestick pullback. Two little
candlestick pullback.
Boom, boom. Boom, boom. That's what the
[__] we can expect to happen.
Now, I could be wrong, but this is what
I'm going to look for in order to enter
this trade. So, in order for me to enter
this trade, I just needed to have a
better engulfing. So, I needed to just
like reject that area again. And if it
closes with an engulfing like this,
I'll pretty much just enter that trade.
It'll be very clean and
very solid. So, what I'm going to do is
put an alarm under that structure level
so I can know when it's going to body
close under. Next, GBP/USD had the move.
So, obviously, we were looking for
shorts yesterday. The shorts never broke
and retested under this area right here,
how I just mentioned. So, with that
happening, we avoided that loss.
Patience [__] pays.
Patience pays. You have to have
patience. If we had taken another one of
these trades, we would have literally
lost. We didn't lose cuz we're patient.
So, this right here is a prime example
of why you need to wait. Now, this is
where we are going to look for buys.
Now, the buys are obviously a little bit
far. Not even going to focus on that.
NZD/USD, which is a trade that we had
for last night. The trade never pulled
back as far as we wanted to to enter the
trade. So, it did end up having the move
exactly how I anticipated, which [__]
sucks. So, literally, out of other
markets that I've been predicting, I've
been pretty much calling literally every
single move.
So, I'll update you guys in the next
hour or more or less if I end up taking
USD/CAD or EUR/AUD. And today I have my
swim shorts on,
you know.
Might go out on the boat today cuz we
got nothing else to do. So, literally, I
don't know, 5 minutes later, this is
currently almost breaking the neckline,
so you guys can see how it's flickering
right now. Well, I It was just breaking
above that neckline, but we still have
27 minutes in order to actually enter
this trade. So, like you see, it's
actually like flickering through like
about a break above, but we cannot enter
a candlestick if it has not closed. This
If it were to close like that, bet I
enter. But it has 27 minutes to actually
close. So, this right now, for all I
know, it could be creating a candlestick
like this. It could be creating a a big
wick or it could be creating a I don't
know. I I have to wait for the 30
minutes to close to see how this closes.
So, this is where a lot of traders make
mistakes that they enter a trade off of
how that candlestick is forming right
now
when it's not a real candlestick. You
can't count that as a bullish engulfing
cuz it's not a bullish engulfing until
it doesn't close. Look. So, like, that
right there, you guys would enter off of
that candlestick and call it, "Yeah,
bullish engulfing." I was like, "Well,
no, it hasn't closed." It's In the next
30 seconds, it can literally just
and become something completely
different.
So, I'll update you guys in 30 minutes.
All right, guys, so I'm on camera duty
right now, so I was at the step out real
quick. But what I'm about to show you
guys is literally one of the lessons
that it took me
probably a year or two to really accept
it and understand and become patient.
And I'm just showing it to you guys on
this video so easily, and it can go
right over a lot of your heads if you're
not in the right headspace to pay
attention and learn from this because
I like It's not about how much money you
can make, it's about how much money I
could save you by just avoiding these
stupid mistakes. And you're going to
make more money by avoiding these stupid
mistakes because you're going to have
more money to bet and risk by not losing
money on these stupid things. Look at
this. So, this, as you can clearly tell,
is about 15 minutes from when we were
last looking at the chart. You can see
there's 12 minutes left in the
candlestick. And you can see how this
did not stay above. It's exactly what I
said. You cannot base a trade off of the
candlestick that has not been fully
closed yet. This candlestick has clearly
now rejected. It has created a fake
push, and as exactly what I said, for
all I know, this candlestick could be
creating a candlestick just like this
one. That's exactly what it did. So,
Alex of 4 years ago would have taken a
loss here because he would have entered
off of that push thinking that that
candlestick was just going to completely
rip through the [__] screen. But no,
that's not the case. You have to wait
for the candlestick to close. And look
at that, we avoided an unnecessary
drawdown, right? Cuz let's say that this
does push from the upside, we avoided
unnecessary drawdown. So, you have to
wait for your entry confirmation. So,
for now, the next step that I'm going to
be waiting for is just same thing. Just
going to be waiting for a body closure
above this retest and then head to the
upside. So, I think it's proper to say
that we should go spend the day at the
boat. We got nothing else to do today.
All right, guys, trade update. So, that
is exactly how the candlestick has
closed. As you guys can see, a new
candlestick has just opened and we have
55 minutes for that one. So, yeah, let
this be a lesson
for waiting for the candlestick to
close. You can't trade a trade off of an
impulse, and that right there is what
experience gives you. So, that right
there shows you why experience pays.
Now, this is something that took me like
2 years to really, really get. So, don't
let this go over your head. Pay
attention. So, we're going to check back
in probably later today. Just waiting
for another retest of that. The other
markets are the exact same spot, kind of
slow day in the markets. So, let's go
out on the boat today and set it and
forget. All right, guys, trade update.
It is currently 4:37 in the afternoon,
so the daily timeframe candlestick is
about to close. As you guys can tell,
we're all sweaty right now because we're
trying to move the Punisher.
It stopped working. So, we thought it
was gas. It did not run out of gas. We
went to go buy a jug of gas, brought it
back, filled it up. We pulled like
pulled it, you know, if you cars that
are manual, if you pull it, you jump
start it through the second first.
Nothing. I think there might be
something with the spark. My opinion,
I'm not a mechanic, but I've [__] up a
lot of cars in the past, and that's what
I think is going on.
So, they're going to take it to the shop
now next to my Rolls-Royce Phantom, next
to my Porsche GT3,
and next to my What are the cars in the
shop? Parking lot's looking a little
empty.
it's looking a little empty, all right?
I feel like I feel like I
I feel like one of these wannabe guru
traders that are trying to blow up right
now. Like, I feel like them right now.
Like, dude, I only have
one Ferrari.
I only one Maybach,
and I only have one $5 million house,
and only one $200,000 AP.
Got to get them rookie numbers up,
buddy. [__] I feel like such a [__]
All I can say is that next video
[laughter]
I mean, I hope it's next video cuz we're
giving them blue balls now. Yeah. No,
it's going to be next video. So, all I
got to say is
next video, I'm going to crack
Uh how do I say this? All I got to say
is that next video, I am not going to
disappoint. This driveway
will no longer be empty. Trust me.
Believe me. Believe me. So, now we're
going to push it back into place. Oh,
and the Cybertruck. Cybertruck right now
is getting service. So, we have four
cars getting service right now. That's
why my driveway is looking kind of weak,
but next week it's going to be on fire.
Uh let's push the car back in. Trade
update, let me show you guys.
Currently, the trade that we're looking
to enter earlier never gave us that
bullish engulfing. We never entered the
trade. We avoided a loss by simply
remaining patient.
Next is GBP/USD.
Price never came back and gave us a
pullback. NZD/USD is gone. The other
trade we're looking to enter is EUR/AUD,
which we have not had the rejection
candlestick that we're looking for. So,
as of right now, no trades for the rest
of the day. Now, we're going to look for
to enter maybe early London session
tonight. So, stay
stay tuned.
Sorry.
[music]
All right. So, we just left Jordan's
house right now. Just to check up on him
to see how he's doing.
Jordan's getting better. It's just, you
know, it's slow recovery. It's his third
time doing the surgery, so
his body just takes longer every single
time to recover.
But, we're going to come back later, do
an ice bath with him,
so he can kind of just get rid of this
inflammation and swelling.
Now, we're going to go hit the gym.
Haven't hit the gym in like 5 days.
[music]
Oh, [__] I'm sweaty.
Oh, [__]
Oh, we're good.
Oh, wow.
That's my M4. It was just raining a
block before. Now, right here is dry.
It's like if nothing ever happened.
This right here, this is our drift
street.
You so So, you guys don't know, I'm
actually legally blind. I I was -7.50
in my eyes. I did LASIK on both eyes,
but I didn't recover 100%, so I'm
probably like -1.25
right now.
Ready?
Never does justice.
[__] trade update, guys. Trade update.
It is currently 1:00 in the morning
right now.
So, dude, I've just been tired. Like,
every single day that I work out, I get
really tired later throughout the day.
But, trade update. Looks like I stayed
up for this time [__] nothing. I hate
staying up too late and literally not
entering a position that I would want to
enter. Let me just show you guys. So,
currently on EUR/AUD,
you guys can see how we've been waiting
for a rejection from this area, and we
did. But, like always, as soon as the
candlestick rejects, I'm I always wait
like for a little bit in order to
confirm the entry, and then pretty much
we did start to have a push back up.
Also, we were not in session. You can
see down here that it was not right
before London session. I always look to
enter a trade right around this time,
which is about to be 1:00 a.m. ideally.
Now, I don't always have to do it, but
it's where I have the best probability
trade.
[music]
So, obviously avoided some drawdown on
this position. I'm still actively
interested in entering it. I'm just
going to probably wait for now another
rejection from up here how we've done
here in the past. Another rejection will
make me want to enter this trade.
USD/CAD, obviously the daily candlestick
closed under, so we avoided that loss to
perfection. I still want to enter the
buy, but once and only we manage to
break and retest above this.
So, something like this, and I'll be
interested in [music] entering this
position, which honestly could happen
this week. Just having a beautiful
4-hour lower low.
So, if this shift would look perfect.
And then, yeah, pretty much everything
else is just waiting for the deeper
retracement. [music] GBP/USD, deep
retracement to buy. NZD/USD,
we are having currently Oh
my god. What the
[__]
Oh, wow. I just saw this right now. So,
NZD/USD
[laughter]
I'm actually laughing because one of my
friends called me earlier. He's like,
"Yo, what should I do with NZD/USD? I
entered earlier this week Sunday night
when you sent it out." This is one of my
friends that I went to high school with.
Literally one of the only close friends
that I have outside of, you know, my
[music] my team.
And then, he told me, he's like, "Yo,
should I close NZD/USD or do I hold?"
[music]
I'm like, "Dude, if you hold, it can
have the risk of having a pullback. I
don't think you should hold. I think you
should close." He's like, "Nah, nah,
nah, nah. I'm going to set and forget."
I'm like,
"Brother,
you have to know when to set and forget
and when to not set and forget. This is
not the time. You don't want to like not
close this trade."
And I'm laughing cuz I know he is I know
I'mma call him. I'mma call him.
Yeah, so I'm that friend that I'll call
you 100 times. I don't give a [__]
Yo. Yo, you're sleeping? Yeah, yeah,
about to go live. Have you seen your
trade?
Yeah, [__] you.
[laughter]
Bro. I'm [__] pissed. [__] me. I told
you, bro. You told me it would have a
pullback, not a whole [__] move
[laughter]
straight down.
This trade is [__] It's what I told
you, bro. I told you it was going to
have a pullback, bro. You don't [__]
listen to me, dog.
What do you think? You told me set and
forget. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. I told you don't set and forget this
trade. It's going to have a pullback.
You didn't listen to me, bro. Yo, no,
no, no, no. I literally told you, bro.
I'm like, "Yo, it's going to have it's
going to have the pullback. If you keep
holding the trade, you're probably going
to get stopped out, dude." No, I know. I
I really don't care. Now, I'm really
going to set and forget. I don't care
anymore.
Oh.
All right. That's on you. All right.
Well, I'll
I'll let you know the next trade.
[laughter]
You [__] better let me know. All
right, all right.
He didn't listen to me. He
You guys
You guys don't get it, you know? But,
it's funny cuz he he doesn't trade. He's
just like, "Bro, dude, you you motivated
me so much off off of your Instagram
stories that I just deposited 500
bucks." He ran it up into like 15,000.
And then, he's like, "You know, I'm
going to take these 15 to like 100." I'm
like, "Yeah?
You sure?
Off of what? You don't know how to
trade." He's like, "Yeah, but I just
copy you." I'm like, "Dude, that's not
how this works. You just You got to
know." So, yeah. So, back to the charts
now. Clearly, NZD/USD is now having a
much deeper retracement than I
anticipated. And I'm actually liking the
buys. I just have to wait for a solid
rejection of this level
uh in order for us to enter this trade.
So, I'm actually going to move this
market to the top with the other ones
cuz I'm very interested in it.
[sighs]
Next is GBP/CAD. No pullback. EUR/USD,
having a push without retracing where I
wanted to. And then, EUR/GBP, not
interested.
So, basically, USD/CAD, waiting for the
break and retest above. EUR/AUD, waiting
for a rejection. And then, NZD/USD,
waiting for a rejection. So, yeah. Yeah,
guys, that is pretty much it. It is
currently pretty much 1:00 in the
morning.
[music]
I am going to knock out probably in the
next 30 to 45 minutes, maybe. I just sit
here in front of the computer, watch
YouTube videos. I get educated on a lot
of stuff.
And uh yeah. So, I'll probably see you
guys tomorrow in the morning. So, I will
see you guys then.
Good morning, ladies and gentlemen.
What do you know about that profitable
trader [__] Market trade update right
now. It's currently 9:30 in the morning.
Last night, you know, it's kind of
funny, right? Because I don't know how
this works or the science behind this.
And if you guys know, let me know in the
comments below. But, it's a little bit
it's a bit it's a bit weird, right? So,
last night I got 5 hours of sleep, and
it says I got 70% recovery.
But, the majority of my sleep was
res- uh what? Like, 2 hours and 47 was
restorative sleep, right? So, then if I
go to yesterday
I slept 6 hours. I took a nap.
And it says 50% recovery. So, I slept
almost
30% more and I got 30% less recovery,
right? I come here to the next day.
Well, this day I really didn't sleep
anything. 4 hours, but still that much.
Then this next day
Look at this. Oh, yeah. 20% recovery.
So, I slept 3 hours that night and then
I took an hour and a half nap.
The day before, slept 4 hours. Yeah, so
I don't really be sleeping at all if you
guys can kind of notice. This is why I
get so much [__] done. I'm literally up
90% of the day. So, those of you guys
that sleep 90% of the day, that's why
you don't get nothing done. But, market
update. So, let me show you guys where
the market is. So, last night you guys
can see that I was waiting for another
confirmation rejection from this level
to enter the trade. That did not happen.
So, we did not enter the trade. Even
though we did get that, it's just not
what I wanted. It's just not It's not
it. Doesn't look like the right price
action or is it enter the trade. So, we
avoided another loss on this market.
Now, what I could be potentially looking
for is going to be for buys. So, if this
daily candlestick body closes above
we're going to wait for a retest to then
buy, exactly how we did right here. Body
close above, retest and then buy. But,
that can probably be something for next
week because we're already on Wednesday.
Uh so, you know technically we only have
about like a day and a half left.
Friday, you don't want to take a trade
on a Friday. That's your AUD. Next is
going to be USD/CAD, which we are still
anticipating for this price to have a
break and retest above. Currently just
moving very very very slow.
Looks like the market momentum is just
slowing down. I mean, look at Look at
Look at this week's price action
versus last week's. Like there's a big
difference. This is where you want to be
trading. This is where you don't want to
be trading.
And last but not least is going to be
NZD/USD. So, it looks like we are having
some type of accumulation from this
area. I don't love the fact that we're
having a ginormous daily bearish
candlestick pullback. And we are going
to potentially close like that cuz that
candlestick only has 7 hours. And I
don't think within 7 hours we can
completely retrace and reject this
level. So, what I want to be waiting for
is to see how the daily candlestick
closes so I can potentially enter this
trade London session tonight. If we keep
accumulating like this, I might be
interested in taking this position. I'm
not super excited about it. I'm just
keeping my eye on it. It looks like the
only active position that the market is
actually giving us. So, this is the only
trade I'm actually looking to enter
depending on how it rejects. GBP/CAD,
just waiting for the pullback. GBP/USD,
waiting for a deeper pullback. So, this
is the the loss that we avoided earlier
this week from here. We had a ginormous
push. Now, we're waiting for a retest of
this level to react, but I actually want
it to retest this level before the other
one.
So, yeah. That's pretty much it.
Um slow week so far. And I told you guys
this at the beginning. I don't know if I
told you guys here. I did tell my
students in the community though cuz I
get live with them every single Sunday.
So, I literally told them like, "Look
guys
I don't want to say we got lucky, but we
timed the beginning of this challenge
very well. So, I was telling the
students that at the beginning of the
week don't approach this week as if it
were to be last week or the week before
or the week before. Like we started the
challenge at a week where the market
momentum was moving so fast and it was
giving so many so much volatility that
it wasn't normal. And you know, you just
simply look left. You statistically look
to the left and you can see that the
moves that were happening in the last
week or two haven't happened in 2 years.
So, keep that energy that hey, just
because it happened these last 2 weeks
doesn't mean that it's going to happen
next week. Cuz you got to look at the
trend. This is a I don't know
black swan event, right? That's what
they call it. That this market has moved
this much in these 2 weeks. And it's
also a black swan event that we started
the challenge on this week. So, it's a
really good start to the challenge, but
it's not the realistic events of what
the market is going to give us for the
following week. So, kind of don't have
that approach to these following weeks
because the market does not have these
type of moves every week. Now, that's
just a higher level of thinking. A lot
of new traders won't understand that. If
you're a new trader, you just literally
won't get it. If you're an experienced
trader, you'll get it. You'll know that
there's good weeks and you'll get it
that there's bad weeks. You just got to
know when to be involved in the good
weeks and when to avoid being involved
in the bad weeks. It's not about being
involved every week. It's about knowing
when to be involved and when to not be
involved. And how do you know that? By
simply having experience and being here
every single week. So, this week and
last week I kind of explained a little
bit of that like, "Look, I don't see
the same market moves that we've been
having at the beginning of the challenge
now. So, we should, you know, sit back a
little bit and wait for those
opportunities to come.
If not, we're going to [__] lose. So,
this week I don't think we might enter a
trade. And if, you know, we do, that'll
be great. If not, we just wait until
next week. I've been 30 days in the
past. I've been a whole month like a
month and a half almost without taking a
position cuz there was just no
opportunities.
I don't think that's going to happen
now, obviously. But I don't know. I'm
just going on a [__] rant right now.
Well, we'll check back in 9:30 in the
morning. We will check back in in
a couple hours.
All right. So, right now trade update.
It's 111, funny enough. But, there's
these kids in the neighborhood that
always pull up. And they just like talk
[__]
They're like fans, but they're like
really nice.
Last time they hustled me, they sold me
some candy. Some cheap ass old candy for
like 100 bucks. Like I got robbed. You
know what? I respect the hustle.
What's up?
We literally just You were home a minute
ago. What's going on?
It's slow. What's going on, dude?
Yeah, this
So, who's this? Charlie. Charlie?
You guys want to see my cat fight it? I
saw it.
You want to see my cat fight it? Yes.
Yes? I want to see it fight. You want to
see it fight? No. No. Yeah?
Bro, it's It's three against one, bro.
It's like
I'm not All right. Let's see how she
acts. It's
It's a lot of them out.
Oh, no.
Oh, he's scared. They're going to get
him. They're going to get him. Oh. Oh, I
didn't hear Oh. Oh.
[laughter]
OH. OH. OH.
OH. OH.
HER NOSE IS CUT. SO, DON'T WORRY. HE'S
NOT HE'S going to stop. Oh, Daniel.
Oh. Oh.
So, yeah. This is my office. This is
where I trade. Do any All right. Do any
of you guys Do any of you guys know how
to trade? No. No. Do you guys know what
trading is? Trading. I know what trading
is. All right. Somebody sit down. Who
wants to be in the You know what my dad
Are you sure you want that spot? Yeah.
You sure? Hey, we saw the videos when
you were like showing the trading. All
right. Is this going to go up or down?
It's going up.
It's going to go up? Raise your hand for
up.
All right. Two up. Raise your hand for
down.
Dude, you haven't even looked at the
charts.
[laughter]
Yes.
All right. So, you think this is going
to go down? Why?
What about this one? Do you think it's
going to go up or down? [music] Right
here. So, price is right here right now.
Do you think it's going to continue
going up or do you think it's going to
go down? I think it's going to go down.
Dude, he's low-key two for two. You
think this is going to go up or down?
I think it's going to go
up.
It's going up. I think it's going to go
up. Dude, they're actually They're
actually getting it, bro. That's
actually kind of crazy. You guys have
not gotten one wrong. Huh?
Yeah, you have not gotten Well, all
right. Like not like the whole move, but
like a piece of the move you guys
haven't. All right. Let's go, boys. I
got to get back into some meetings. Got
to get back to some work.
Trade update. It's currently like 5:00.
No trades to right now.
Going to play some basketball
and hit the gym.
So.
But, I'll make it backwards.
You didn't make it, though.
It's crazy that the community is in
English, Spanish, all over the world.
It's crazy.
Now, I got to make this now.
I made it.
I know I I actually did make it.
[laughter]
All right, ladies and gentlemen. Market
update. It is currently 9:04
in the morning, Thursday morning.
You know what I've realized? This week
has just consisted of dodging bullets.
Like we've been off [__] week like
pew pew pew. Like literally
Uh let me make sure this is not
All week has consisted of dodging
bullets. Now, yes, this is a real gun.
It's never been shot. It's never been
loaded. Don't worry for the people in
the comments that are going to be
sensitive. I know how to handle some
type of weapons. So, yeah. I I I I've
gotten trained on how to handle weapons.
I am very educated on weapons. I respect
weapons very dearly. Um
I have many weapons. So, for all of you
guys in the comments that are going to
be sensitive, don't worry. I
I've been educated on it.
But, yeah. This week has consisted of
dodging bullets. Uh we have had some
trades that we could have entered. And
obviously they were on the higher risk
side of it. Currently right now, you
guys can see that the account is exactly
the same. We have not executed any
trades so far, which kind of annoying
because we took a stupid loss last week
and now this week we
the same losses we took last week that
were counter trend trades, we could have
taken them this week that would have
made us the money cuz that's what the
majority of this week has consisted of
counter trend trades and price having
pullbacks. But it's okay, it is what it
is. Lessons, everything happens for a
reason.
But this has been dodging bullets. We've
just been missing all these different
types of trades. So, let me show you
guys. So, to start off is going to be
Euro No, NZD USD. So, yesterday we
anticipated for price having a pullback
and then obviously we're looking to
enter at this area. If you notice, I've
been calling all these pullbacks
perfectly. It's been getting right to
the area. It's been giving the
engulfing, which is the entry signal.
But then obviously, you know, we don't
have the full shift of the structure and
everything we're looking for to enter
the trade. Like we do have it here, but
I mean this happened at
5:00 in the morning, dude. I was knocked
out at 5:00 in the morning.
So, this is a trade that I would have
possibly taken, but again, missed it
because of the time zone. I've been
dodging bullets all week on this.
Another pair is going to be Euro AUD.
So, Euro AUD, we were looking to enter
the sells here about a day or two ago.
Then we had the break. Then on this
pullback, we were looking for a buy. Now
we broke under and then we're looking
for the sell. Now we're breaking back
above and now we could be looking for
the buy. It has just been an absolute
[__] show. All right, next is going to
be USD CAD.
So, USD CAD, we had the pullback of this
level of area of interest, the morning
star formation, rejection from this
level. And then again, avoided that loss
because we had the push to the downside,
no shift of structure. But now we're
under this area of interest. Whenever
we're under, we're going down. Whenever
we're under, we're going down. Under
down, under down, under down. So, we
can't buy if we are under. It looks like
we're breaking above, which is where
we're going to be looking to enter this
trade. And after it breaks above, which
is this right here, we're going to then
have a retest. So, we avoided a loss
here on this area, avoided an an
unnecessary loss here. We were looking
to sell simply because we were under.
It's just been, I'm telling you, a
[__]
So,
what are the trades that we could be
possibly taking now? For sure, GBP going
to be ready for this week. GBP CAD is
going to be ready for next week as well.
We had the break, but never had the
retest.
Euro USD, look at this. It's just having
a major pullback this year. Like I don't
even Like I'm not even looking at
Euro GBP is now finally having the
pullback as well. So, I say the main
focus could be GBP USD for a deeper
retracement right around here to go
long.
NZD USD possibly at a retest to go
short. So, we're going to remove this
and remove this cuz we're no longer
looking for that.
Now we can do is look for a retest of
this neckline of the head and shoulders,
retest of the round psychological level
60,000, retest of the EMA, retest of
previous structure level
then after the downside. So, you guys
are seeing how it looks good. Like
that's why you have to find these killer
support and resistance zones because
whenever you're above it, you're just
ready to buy. Whenever you're under it,
you're just ready to sell. That's I say
that's why it's the second most
important thing. The first most
important thing is trend. Second most
important thing is going to be the area
of interest. So, Euro No, NZD USD,
that's what I'm looking for. Euro AUD
is same thing, you know, we're going to
be waiting for a rejection from here.
This is probably the only trade that I
could take maybe today
depending how it closes.
Um and then USD CAD, we just got to wait
for a retest. So, I'd put Euro AUD as
number one,
NZD USD [music] as number two, GBP USD
as number three.
So, you guys are seeing Oh, exactly what
I [__] said.
[snorts]
Look at this. We Remember that channel
that I drew out that I had to take out
because it was pissing me off at the
beginning of the week? Well, look at
that. How about now? Hm? How about now?
You see this? The same theory that I
had. We have this humongous channel. We
then break out of it, we retest it and
then we head to the upside. You look at
it now here in GBP USD. The ginormous
channel, we break out of it, we are now
retesting it and then we're going to
have the push to the upside.
Wow.
Set and forget. Once again, giving you
guys Well, that's crazy.
Patience, patience, patience. That is
literally the key to this. Just waiting
for all this to play out.
So, today we have podcasts. Um I'm going
to go tour a penthouse. I'm going to be
getting a penthouse very soon here in
Brickell, Brickell, Miami.
Um
and then Sensei is going to go buy some
cars. We're just going to go with him. I
think my car is almost ready. We might
pull up and see it. I might give you
guys a little sneak peek.
And then after that we are going to see
where the day takes us. So, take a ride
with us today on a little vlog that we
have cuz there's no trades that are
going to be ready anytime soon from what
I'm seeing here. So, it's a little vlog
day that we have to do today. So,
podcast, penthouse tour, and then new
cars. All right, guys, trade update as
of right now, still no trade in the
account. It's 11:30 in the morning.
GBP USD is having somewhat of the move.
So, we can kind of see that it's having
a rejection. I did not expect that for
it to happen right now, which kind of
sucks. So, we're going to see if we can
possibly enter that later today maybe. I
don't like entering trade I mean
the last time that I like entering a
trade is Thursday night so that Friday
morning hopefully has a push and then we
can just close right before market
close. If I'm not in a good amount of
profit, I don't want to hold for the
following week. So, I don't know. We'll
see how it goes. Right now we're on our
way to do a podcast with the students.
After the student podcast, we're going
to go eat early on a fast and then after
we eat, we're going to go look at the
new penthouse that we might potentially
add to the collection of [__] that we
have.
And
the [__] out the way, dude. Oh, by the
way, for those of you guys that don't
know, the Ferrari has the craziest horn.
So, this not beep here.
The horn is literally like right here.
So,
So, and then there's also one on this
side right here. So, you have like both
your thumbs.
So, after we look at the penthouse,
we're going to then go watch Sensei buy
new cars and we're going to go see if my
new car is ready. So, we'll update you
guys as the day goes.
[music]
Yeah, we are not. We're not waiting
that. Not happening. This is how we do
it.
I mean, so the these are all NPCs,
right? Like like I'll give you a perfect
example, right? I guarantee you this
next car is just a It's just somebody
automated.
That might be a cop.
This other in drive, whatever this is,
right? Whatever this is.
It's just It's not a real person. It's
just a bot that they're just driving.
No, they're just not driving anywhere.
You know like when you enter the lobby
room in GTA and it's just cars driving
going nowhere. Same thing. People are
just driving. It's not real and it won't
affect any of their journey cuz they're
not going anywhere. Like I can just cut
Like I can just cut off this car right
here.
Nothing happens, right? It's just
They're NPCs.
All right, so we're going to be looking
at literally that top floor up there.
See that top top top top top top top
floor?
Yeah, we're going to be looking at the
one right under.
[laughter]
No, it's not this building, but we are
literally going to be at the top top top
floor. You guys are going to see now in
just a second after this podcast. It's
crazy. Like I Like where I live right
now, it's a very suburbs area, far from
the city, which is where everything is
going on right now.
And I
And whenever I got to do something, I
got to always drive to the city. It's
like 45 minutes. I'm like, "Dude, you
know what? I'm I'm tired of this, right?
Let's just Let's just get a spot in the
city. Whenever I want to stay there, I
stay there. Whenever I want to stay far
away, I stay far away." Because, bro,
it's not It's not worth this commuting
every time. This is 45 minutes right
now, no traffic. Like if there's
traffic, it'll be
easily an hour something for sure. So,
fun. Oh oh [__] Holy [__] Wait, so you
you're doing like your own make [__]
So, I basically I've changed it to
Trading Made Simple. So, TMS. [__]
that's sick. Yeah, cuz that that's my
logo right there, like the S. And then
you added the TMS. Sick.
Yeah, cuz I think your logo's hard.
Profitable trader. That's all they need
to know.
All right, what No, what kind of foods
do you like and I'll recommend you to a
spot?
Anything. What what what what do you
like to eat?
I like sushi.
You like sushi? There's a good sushi
place. I've never had it, but I'll try
it. You've never had sushi? No. I tried
I tried fish last night. So, I had
crab cakes. Hold [laughter] on. Hold on.
shrimp. So,
you've never had sushi? No. We're We're
going to go eat some sushi after here,
bro. I'm going to actually invite you to
some sushi. You have you ever used
chopsticks?
No.
I tried. They're hard.
All right, first [music] in this
attempt, we haven't taught him anything.
How do you pick it up?
[laughter]
I thought I might have traded. We got to
teach how to use chopsticks.
Now you're going to move inside and
you're going to add this one on top.
So you're going to leave the middle
finger up.
Yeah, yeah, but [music and singing] not
not up here. Uh you want to be back over
here. Like the further the better.
So then like this. Are you just You just
use the middle one to go and grab it?
Yeah, literally exactly how you're doing
it.
Just go in and you just grab it.
You're a quick learner.
Really good? Perfect. Yeah. So this
[music] is a Wagyu Gyoza with some
truffle. Have you ever had truffles?
Nope.
You guys know that we're making these,
right?
[music]
So this is truffle right here? Truffle
is like a It's like a butter.
So get the truffle. Just try it like
that.
[music]
Yeah, yeah.
Good, right?
It's like an interesting taste. It
tastes better with food.
See, look, you're now you're a natural,
bro.
All right, go. First one.
It's good?
Take your virginity.
Didn't you hurt yourself that you've
never been in a high building, no?
How does this feel, bro? We're literally
at the top of Miami.
[music]
Trade up there right now. It is
currently
3:55 in the afternoon.
Still no trade.
Yeah, I I couldn't drive the Ferrari.
Now we we'd be sink.
Wait, coño.
Oh, wow.
It's literally sinking.
Yeah, so my Miami has a flood hazard.
It sucks.
Every trade from you I get [__]
smacked from behind, dude.
to win on both. You always win on both.
Do me dirty. Like a dirty [__]
All right, so we'll flip we'll flip a
coin 175 160. 165 170, yes. And uh how
about the GT3? How much you want? What
you pay? [__] 350 grand? I pay 400.
[laughter]
What do you owe? I owe 230. 230? Or you
want me to go to business?
Bobby, I want to be here. I got to be
got You know, I want to be able to do
this with you guys.
Woah, woah, okay, okay, okay. Hold on.
Let He talks fast. That's the trick,
hey. That's the trick that they do. 165
170. That's done. We shake hands. 240
250. I'll go with the coin.
Good. Of course.
[laughter]
This is what I do. Done deal. Hey JC,
give me give me my lucky quarter that's
double-sided, okay? All right, Ariel.
All right. You did donuts right here.
I I feel that they have something. Oh,
okay.
Go ahead.
Tails never fails, [__]
Tails.
What is it?
Tails. Let's go.
Okay, go again.
All right, this is
This is [laughter] for the Maybach.
TAILS.
[laughter]
SO 170 AND 240? ALL RIGHT, MAN.
LET'S GO, HUH?
DON'T YOU LIKE THAT?
250 165. Let's go. Who's your daddy? Why
not? You won this one.
[laughter]
Yeah, it always lands on tails. It
always lands on tails.
[laughter]
I'm going to tell you something. The
proper way to do a coin toss is you get
You're supposed to let it fall.
That's the proper way to do it. See,
look, heads.
That's the proper way. This was easy. I
was like, all right, cool. I'm not going
to say nothing.
Heads.
You hear the problem, Bobby?
Hey Bobby, the money came to friends.
That's all that matters. Come on. Trade
update. So right now, trade update EUR
AUD, haven't had the rejection that I
want in order to take this trade to the
upside. NZD USD, just consolidating, not
interested. May might be interested in
buys if we break above this above.
GBP USD, currently has not had a
pullback, so I've not been able to enter
a trade. USD CAD has not had the break
above how we wanted it.
And then GBP CAD is just something ready
for next week. All right, guys. So
waking up a little late today. Actually
not really. Currently is 9:15 in the
morning.
Today's going to be a crazy day. Today
is going to be a long day. We got a lot
of [__] going on. So we have Jay and
Juice coming today. He came all the way
from Canada. He canceled the trip to go
see his family in the Middle East to
come see me instead of going to see his
family, which
crazy. So we're going to actually bring
him with us to go get the car, the new
car that I have just gotten, and I'm
telling you right now the new car that I
have gotten is more expensive than this
house that I'm in right now. Yesterday
we took the previous student to go the
podcast to go eat, and then we went to
go tour the penthouse with him. Now this
student we're going to go pick up my new
with Oh, yeah. [__] I said the name.
Well, did they blur it out? Um so if
you're not part of the Swing Trading Lab
student community, you're missing out.
So let me give you guys a the recap for
the week. So as of right now, we did not
take absolutely any trades this week,
which kind of sucks because it somewhat
sets us back a little bit from the
momentum that we had going. And there
was great opportunities this week in the
market, but we just simply did not enter
any of them, and they were missed, and
we did avoid a lot of losses. So let's
get into it. So to start off, we'll
start off with EUR AUD. So EUR AUD, we
originally started off the week
interested on sells once price had
retested [music] this level. Avoided the
losses. Then once price had to the
upside, we waited for a pullback to then
buy. Avoided one of these losses as
well. And then we were looking to sell
down here, and then it decided to start
having a push up, so we avoided three
losses on EUR AUD that we were
interested in taking just by buying
above the support level and selling
under this resistance level. All right,
next is going to be NZD USD. So earlier
this week we anticipated price to have a
push from this area to the upside. We
never had the pullback as deep as we
wanted to, so we missed that trade. Then
when it pulled back, we were
anticipating to enter the buy here. If
we would have entered this buy here, it
would have been something like this, and
we would have probably gotten stopped
out, so we avoided this loss, but now it
looks like the actual trade is having
the momentum that it does for it to head
to the upside, which is good because
this trade is going to probably be my
number one pair for next week. All I'm
going to simply be waiting for for this
pair for next week is going to be for a
quick retest of this area for it to then
head to the upside. So this is NZD USD.
Next is GBP USD, which once again we
have this channel right here. Price
broke out of the channel, retested the
level of resistance, retested the level
of support, headed to the upside
beautifully, exactly how EUR USD did it.
We had the channel, we broke out to the
upside, we then had the retest, and then
we took the trade to the upside. So this
trade was actually missed. I should have
[__] taken this trade right here,
which would have been a beautiful This
would have taken it somewhere in the
middle of this candlestick here. So this
high right now would have been easy a
one to 2.5 risk to reward. But it is
what it is. My anticipation is next week
after this very strong weekly
candlestick, it's going to have a
pullback, then the next week it's going
to head to the upside, and blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah, right? So daily
timeframe, it looks very, very, very
clean. We're going to leave this here
because, you know, I do this like what
When I'm giving you guys a quick recap
right now is what I do every single
Sunday with my students, but in detail.
So I do the whole recap of what the week
was like, and then I anticipate the
following week with the new trades that
we're interested in taking. So
GBP USD, had the breakout, had the
retest, is now heading to the upside. I
think it could come back, retest, and
continue heading to the upside. This
market structure is very, very clean. So
this is another market that we
predicted, but we missed. And then this
sell from right here, we actually
avoided that loss right at the beginning
of the week.
Next is USD CAD. So USD CAD, we were
anticipating for price to have a
rejection from here and head to the
upside. We avoided this loss because of
this very strong bearish candlestick if
we would have obviously taken this trade
right around here. And now it looks like
it's accumulating at this area where it
can potentially head to the downside, or
if it breaks and retests, it could head
to the upside, which is truthfully
the ideal situation. But for this one
we're going to have to sit on our hands
and see what the market is going to do.
GBP CAD, price did have the break above
how we wanted to, never retested it, and
then EUR GBP is going to be a trade that
we're going to be interested in on this
following next week. So you guys got to
tune in to next week to see exactly what
this market is going to do. It's very
easy, right? We have level support,
support, support. We broke it, retested
it. We're going to look to buy at this
area. It's pretty simple. And then
lastly, Bitcoin, right? So I've never
done Bitcoin here on YouTube, I believe.
I strongly do believe that Bitcoin is
going to have a rejection from this
area, head to around here. If you notice
I have multiple different alarms
notifying me of areas where I want to
buy. So I am not a BTC trader. I don't
know how to trade BTC, but I am looking
to invest some funds into BTC. And this
is something that I literally do every
single Sunday with my students. It's
part of the Set and Forget community. If
you want to know more about it, the link
is in the description below. But I
literally share with my students the
trades, the investments that I'm looking
to do every single Sunday. It's a live
Zoom call. You can literally ask
questions directly to me
of whatever market it is you want me to
break down, whatever questions you may
have. I answer every single week, and I
give you the top markets I'm going to be
trading for the week ahead on this exact
challenge. So, if you literally copy the
trades that I am [music] sending out,
you're going to have the same results as
me. The student from yesterday I was I'm
copying the 100 to a mil challenge. I
put in a grand in it instead. I'm at
like 30k I think right now.
That's crazy.
I thought I'd copy that and I thought if
I can get that to a mil, that would be
insane. Do you know what I mean? That's
a massive live account because I don't
risk 1% per trade either cuz I think
it's [__] He literally said he
turned $1,000 to $30,000 following the
same exact trades that he's been seeing
on Sunday Swings, which is absolutely
legendary and that's the fourth person
that has done that. So, it's a four for
four. Out of the four people that have
joined this podcast, four of them are
having the same results copying the same
exact trades that they get on Sunday
Swings, which is sick. So, if you want
to know more about that, the link is in
the description below and yeah, now Jay
and Juice is going to pull up in about a
couple of hours and then after that,
we're going to bring him with us to go
see the
Oh, you could blur it out.
Yeah, so we're going to we bought a
[__]
Now, if you can guess the color of this
if you can guess the interior, if you
can guess the What What else? If you can
guess the the mileage on this
you win. I know you win. What do you
win?
So, we're going to bring Jay and Juice
with us to go pick up
because it is going to be a crazy
experience for him and yesterday we took
the student with us to go see the new
penthouse that we were looking to do and
today, you know what? I like giving this
experience to you guys out there because
you guys trust in me and I'm like, you
know what? Let me just give you guys the
access to this lifestyle that you guys
can very easily obtain by simply showing
up every single day. So, Jay and Juice
literally did not go see his family to
come see me. So, I'm going to make sure
I made this experience worth it. So,
[music] just stay tuned for another day
in the life with me.
All right. So, currently right now it is
3:54 in 3:50 in the afternoon. So, Jay
and Juice is literally about to pull up.
So, he pulled up late. He was supposed
to pull up earlier for a podcast. Pulled
up late. So, what we're going to do is
we're going to go now to TPT, pick up a
watch and then we're going to go
straight to go pick up the Bugatti. So,
Jay and Juice is a student from the
30-day boot camp and has had one of the
craziest results anybody from the boot
camp. And we're about to meet him right
now in person. Jay and Juice is balling
out here, huh?
Yeah, dude. You know it's real when your
students pull up on a crazy Look at you,
lady.
What's up?
Oh. Yo, what the [__] Yo.
I didn't turn it off cuz I don't know
where you want me to park it.
Tell him, brother. What's up, man? I
hear that accent, bro. Really?
of my boys is from Montreal.
From Montreal? Yeah, from Montreal.
Really? Yeah, downtown, man.
Yeah, he has the same accent as you do.
That's why My accent is not Canadian.
No? No. I've like I've only been there
for like 3 years since then. Oh, what
the [__] You picked it up mighty quick.
All right. So, we're we're on on a time
constraint.
Um where do we Where Where do I park?
No, no. You got to follow us. I follow
you. Okay. Follow us to
We're going to go to Neil TPT and then
So, we're supposed to do the Wait, do
you know what we're doing today or not?
Yeah, yeah. I know. Barely.
[laughter]
Yeah, we lost Jay and Juice.
So, I like putting people's driving
skills to the test.
How good or bad people are.
Oh, he's Oh, he's behind us.
There's a key on how to like actually
like race. Like the the point is not
acceleration or deceleration. The point
is handling. Like everything I've just
done right now is pretty much the car in
like neutral. It's just like
Where you at?
I'm coming. I need like 9 minutes.
Yeah, you can't do this [__] cuz this
car is not mine. Like I can't drive the
way you're driving it.
I know. I know. No, no, no. I taught you
how to trade. I'll teach you how to
drive soon. I'll teach you how to drive.
Yeah, yeah. I got it. I got it. I got
it. So, I'm coming.
All right, man. All right. I'll see you
there. So, literally right now we're
going to [__] go up, pick up the
and then Insane. Like literally like
right now. I'll show you some watches,
bro. Like only RM cuz you have
everything else now. You have Rolex, you
have AP. Patek is not
Uh
yeah, yeah. Maybe you can do a Patek one
day. I'll just show you a good just to
keep you entertained.
But this this is still my favorite
piece, dude.
[snorts]
If you did want it, bro, I'd hook you
up, honestly.
On that because I have two.
You got you. This is insane. Insane
factory diamonds. Like the baby blue
looks so good.
I know. I know.
And the price is good on that, too.
And that's that's a bubble, right? Yeah,
factory. You don't have any bubbles or
bubbles? Yeah, these are bubbles.
Up here. Black with white? Oh. Very nice
combo. You can put white crown and black
with red. The black ones are limited
editions. Yeah, they're worth 150. Is
not? What's up with this big ass? That's
a solid gold 1103. And that's the solid
So, look, they make it in in titanium
rose. So, the top B rose and the side
titanium. This is the solid gold case.
And it's actually like a $50,000
difference, Alex, for the sides to be
gold, but people notice it. Like if
you're wearing that, it's like it's the
most solid 11 you can buy. The solid
gold. How much is this, bro? I'll hook
you up. I got you. Here we go. Here we
go. Here you go. I'll hook you up. I'll
hook you up. He's going to go on the
He's going to go on the marketplace.
to sign papers just like him, bro. He's
going to go on the marketplace and add
50,000.
Look at my chain, bro. Oh, it's lit,
dude.
You set and forget with this, bro. Oh,
so
black and blue? Nah. Orange? Nowhere
near. Nowhere near. Nowhere near.
[laughter]
Yeah, I'm not saying. Let's just say
it's pink. You won't be disappointed.
I would be disappointed in pink, though,
if it's
[laughter]
Just buy something.
Okay. Okay. But why Why would you be
disappointed?
Cuz who buys
makes it pink, bro? Do it with the
Porsche
[laughter]
But then so, when somebody says, "You
know what? I don't like the color
Like what color is it then?
[laughter]
[music]
That's how I bought my new car. So, you
didn't Yeah, you you didn't know what
car it was, right? You don't No. All
right. You better know how to live it.
So, like I was going to I was just going
to do this by myself, you know, but I'm
like, dude, you're one of the students
from the 30-day boot camp. I'm going to
give you like a little bit of an insight
into the lifestyle.
Crazy this one, yeah?
Yeah, it's a crazy Yeah? Yeah.
Dude, trust me. It's the craziest [__]
ever. You're going to trip out.
Yeah, I know. Cuz me, I love cars like
Oh, dude, you're going to trip out.
This guy's not going to not [laughter]
going to expect that.
But this is what like an everyday kind
of looks like, bro. We're on missions
all [__] day, bro.
So, I was going to say something and say
some words of courage, but all I have to
say is
set and forget. That's all I got to say.
You think, bro?
I have no words to say, honestly. And
it's
You're the only one that knows, bro.
No, no, no.
I I I'm speechless, honestly. I'm not
going to say anything. I'll I'll I'll
I'll leave it for you guys to see it.